{
    "subject": "resource/Teenage_Kicks",
    "predicate": "property/length",
    "object": "96.0",
    "human_readable": "The length of Teenage Kicks is 96.0.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7806437611579895,
            "question": "What is the length of Teenage Kicks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5290814638137817,
            "question": "What unit of measurement is used for the length of Teenage Kicks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5045003890991211,
            "question": "Could you express the length of Teenage Kicks in minutes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4879145920276642,
            "question": "Does the length of Teenage Kicks suggest it's a fast or slow song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4467422068119049,
            "question": "How long is the song Teenage Kicks in seconds?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42090120911598206,
            "question": "How does the length of Teenage Kicks compare to other popular songs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38903751969337463,
            "question": "Is Teenage Kicks a short or long song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3546827435493469,
            "question": "What musical composition has a duration of 96.0?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35045138001441956,
            "question": "What factors might influence the length of a song like Teenage Kicks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3254958391189575,
            "question": "If a song needs to be at least 3 minutes long, is Teenage Kicks long enough?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The length of Teenage Kicks is 96.0.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1128_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What factors might influence the length of a song like Teenage Kicks?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1128_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What musical composition has a duration of 96.0?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1128_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Teenage Kicks a short or long song?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1128_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1128_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1128_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1128_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1128_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1128_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1128_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1128_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1128_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1128_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1128_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The information provided does not mention any specific song length for \"Teenage Kicks.\" Therefore, the statement that its length is 96 minutes (assuming 96 refers to minutes) cannot be supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}